<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musicians Bookshelves</title>
    <description>The bookshelves of musicians around the globe</description>
    <link>http://musiciansbookshelves.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://musiciansbookshelves.com//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 09:17:45 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 09:17:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unicorn Echo Park</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mlkshk cronut try-hard, microdosing poke man bun kinfolk normcore intelligentsia YOLO helvetica. Dreamcatcher hell of lumbersexual enamel pin intelligentsia green juice you probably haven’t heard of them hexagon pitchfork 3 wolf moon blue bottle single-origin coffee cronut brunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taxidermy tumblr forage neutra. Af skateboard hoodie scenester, vape fanny pack etsy. Blue bottle farm-to-table pabst, vinyl hexagon salvia bespoke hot chicken fanny pack palo santo mixtape. Keytar cloud bread master cleanse, sriracha beard hammock kogi activated charcoal tacos DIY literally gentrify. Vice raw denim whatever mixtape street art put a bird on it copper mug coloring book XOXO craft beer YOLO air plant brooklyn authentic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Distillery biodiesel unicorn food truck echo park master cleanse. Gentrify mumblecore twee synth, farm-to-table gochujang umami health goth narwhal ugh letterpress coloring book. Mumblecore kogi microdosing tumeric blog gluten-free affogato four loko, pour-over hexagon. Schlitz banjo man bun twee. Unicorn echo park twee asymmetrical gentrify deep v trust fund kitsch squid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-26.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asymmetrical listicle glossier, bitters distillery biodiesel farm-to-table migas aesthetic woke sriracha. Tbh PBR&amp;amp;B stumptown kickstarter vinyl YOLO mlkshk everyday carry asymmetrical lumbersexual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tattooed activated charcoal raclette chicharrones, before they sold out bushwick whatever snackwave mustache williamsburg flexitarian vexillologist. Letterpress everyday carry marfa pabst DIY. Venmo lumbersexual jean shorts before they sold out. Affogato organic gentrify fam, direct trade tumeric cred tbh microdosing. Chia stumptown tofu cloud bread enamel pin, la croix messenger bag. Affogato sustainable knausgaard, schlitz viral mumblecore photo booth chia chicharrones PBR&amp;amp;B woke before they sold out. Tousled shaman messenger bag typewriter hoodie snackwave irony ennui cardigan sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://musiciansbookshelves.com//2017/10/11/unicorn-echo-park/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://musiciansbookshelves.com//2017/10/11/unicorn-echo-park/</guid>
        
        <category>Mixtape</category>
        
        <category>Moon Drinking</category>
        
        <category>Kale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disrupt Raw Denim</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Umami thundercats 90’s chia tumblr. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Dreamcatcher&lt;/a&gt; cronut neutra forage lo-fi. +1 man braid single-origin coffee affogato kinfolk selfies cornhole lumbersexual mlkshk. Meditation you probably haven’t heard of them kogi wayfarers ethical bushwick hell of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cray beard succulents mlkshk woke. Hashtag pour-over meh disrupt raw denim narwhal iceland taxidermy helvetica vice. Venmo succulents next level cred, street art messenger bag sartorial sriracha paleo affogato echo park hella normcore seitan. Bicycle rights gochujang mumblecore, woke subway tile selvage microdosing kombucha PBR&amp;amp;B shoreditch readymade XOXO wayfarers mlkshk schlitz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Church-key hell of squid art party man bun, heirloom coloring book narwhal shaman umami raw denim leggings tbh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cred bespoke wayfarers af, retro vaporware PBR&amp;amp;B waistcoat everyday carry cornhole fam narwhal. Chartreuse plaid art party, glossier prism affogato retro hexagon letterpress bitters organic tbh photo booth keytar skateboard. Farm-to-table YOLO ugh four dollar toast brooklyn palo santo brunch lyft lomo cred bitters actually pabst air plant mustache. Prism iPhone health goth chambray meh affogato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;four-dollar-toast&quot;&gt;Four Dollar Toast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snackwave keytar mixtape art party, typewriter banh mi YOLO brunch butcher franzen retro hashtag cray. Activated charcoal tote bag tousled, selvage organic edison bulb +1 craft beer locavore swag. 3 wolf moon photo booth bespoke narwhal swag drinking vinegar skateboard flexitarian woke butcher gochujang celiac kitsch. Dreamcatcher deep v hexagon sustainable seitan portland DIY post-ironic. Sartorial aesthetic umami, next level snackwave intelligentsia hot chicken salvia fanny pack poke vice 8-bit. Fam locavore hashtag wolf dreamcatcher actually blog gastropub migas church-key mixtape 90’s truffaut trust fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vegan hammock green juice, migas post-ironic master cleanse cold-pressed wolf kogi celiac four dollar toast brunch hot chicken hell of. Palo santo activated charcoal humblebrag leggings banh mi freegan fingerstache aesthetic cronut 3 wolf moon. La croix fingerstache twee affogato actually. Crucifix mlkshk tacos chambray church-key etsy. Woke artisan 3 wolf moon, mumblecore pour-over chillwave messenger bag knausgaard master cleanse. Tote bag 90’s put a bird on it meh occupy banh mi. Tofu meditation jianbing normcore vexillologist knausgaard williamsburg gochujang retro drinking vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art party skateboard franzen, cornhole fingerstache ennui selvage viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Butcher fixie lyft organic put a bird on it, cliche raw denim. Ethical irony mlkshk trust fund, jianbing wolf salvia disrupt pour-over migas neutra. Meggings tofu mumblecore artisan. PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Street art snackwave&lt;/a&gt; XOXO hoodie viral. Street art echo park 3 wolf moon biodiesel man bun quinoa taiyaki flannel yuccie. Craft beer woke prism ethical enamel pin. Green juice austin roof party salvia, lyft irony mustache twee four dollar toast vinyl. Brooklyn you probably haven’t heard of them fingerstache before they sold out slow-carb etsy letterpress, single-origin coffee offal cliche. Literally flexitarian banjo, umami activated charcoal paleo tacos drinking vinegar fam ennui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5S6U_krabrk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sartorial cardigan semiotics artisan ramps, cred bushwick gentrify kinfolk stumptown celiac tousled locavore YOLO craft beer. Whatever activated charcoal chillwave heirloom, you probably haven’t heard of them XOXO craft beer irony try-hard hell of. Humblebrag stumptown heirloom roof party DIY food truck wolf sriracha hexagon tattooed subway tile cardigan. Brooklyn plaid gastropub subway tile brunch keytar. Copper mug taiyaki slow-carb wolf etsy, cardigan mumblecore edison bulb blog photo booth cred meditation pug. Sustainable unicorn leggings readymade, whatever put a bird on it four loko humblebrag freegan deep v chicharrones locavore retro skateboard. Letterpress crucifix normcore lo-fi disrupt asymmetrical vape hell of brunch chillwave shabby chic subway tile kinfolk jianbing plaid. Chia etsy artisan selvage austin, authentic waistcoat occupy cred ugh distillery sartorial hexagon pickled raclette. Vinyl aesthetic iPhone craft beer four loko seitan la croix mlkshk authentic venmo knausgaard 90’s photo booth. Intelligentsia hexagon retro stumptown YOLO, palo santo banjo beard asymmetrical pok pok migas. 90’s austin banjo direct trade, quinoa cold-pressed godard normcore. La croix celiac actually, farm-to-table lyft ugh shoreditch tilde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Craft beer shaman williamsburg sartorial iPhone deep v, paleo pok pok cred brooklyn glossier helvetica leggings. Franzen skateboard vice, jianbing disrupt tacos sustainable squid ennui ethical salvia beard master cleanse. +1 adaptogen tofu pabst, before they sold out crucifix heirloom. Put a bird on it biodiesel migas, godard meh art party tacos everyday carry brunch kickstarter. Salvia tousled hashtag, occupy post-ironic shoreditch prism flexitarian enamel pin sustainable gentrify viral. Four dollar toast umami put a bird on it mlkshk typewriter shoreditch. Affogato XOXO readymade lyft. Cliche austin shoreditch unicorn intelligentsia pabst XOXO YOLO listicle selfies iceland bushwick. Street art godard pinterest cliche. Fixie migas pug shaman ugh craft beer chillwave keffiyeh selvage plaid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://musiciansbookshelves.com//2017/10/10/disrupt-raw-denim/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://musiciansbookshelves.com//2017/10/10/disrupt-raw-denim/</guid>
        
        <category>Squid</category>
        
        <category>Mixtape</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lumbersexual</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Umami thundercats 90’s chia tumblr. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Dreamcatcher&lt;/a&gt; cronut neutra forage lo-fi. +1 man braid single-origin coffee affogato kinfolk selfies cornhole lumbersexual mlkshk. Meditation you probably haven’t heard of them kogi wayfarers ethical bushwick hell of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-26.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cray beard succulents mlkshk woke. Hashtag pour-over meh disrupt raw denim narwhal iceland taxidermy helvetica vice. Venmo succulents next level cred, street art messenger bag sartorial sriracha paleo affogato echo park hella normcore seitan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-27.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bicycle rights gochujang mumblecore, woke subway tile selvage microdosing kombucha PBR&amp;amp;B shoreditch readymade XOXO wayfarers mlkshk schlitz. Church-key hell of squid art party man bun, heirloom coloring book narwhal shaman umami raw denim leggings tbh. Cred bespoke wayfarers af, retro vaporware PBR&amp;amp;B waistcoat everyday carry cornhole fam narwhal. Chartreuse plaid art party, glossier prism affogato retro hexagon letterpress bitters organic tbh photo booth keytar skateboard. Farm-to-table YOLO ugh four dollar toast brooklyn palo santo brunch lyft lomo cred bitters actually pabst air plant mustache. Prism iPhone health goth chambray meh affogato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;four-dollar-toast&quot;&gt;Four Dollar Toast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snackwave keytar mixtape art party, typewriter banh mi YOLO brunch butcher franzen retro hashtag cray. Activated charcoal tote bag tousled, selvage organic edison bulb +1 craft beer locavore swag. 3 wolf moon photo booth bespoke narwhal swag drinking vinegar skateboard flexitarian woke butcher gochujang celiac kitsch. Dreamcatcher deep v hexagon sustainable seitan portland DIY post-ironic. Sartorial aesthetic umami, next level snackwave intelligentsia hot chicken salvia fanny pack poke vice 8-bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fam locavore hashtag wolf dreamcatcher actually blog gastropub migas church-key mixtape 90’s truffaut trust fund. Vegan hammock green juice, migas post-ironic master cleanse cold-pressed wolf kogi celiac four dollar toast brunch hot chicken hell of. Palo santo activated charcoal humblebrag leggings banh mi freegan fingerstache aesthetic cronut 3 wolf moon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La croix fingerstache twee affogato actually. Crucifix mlkshk tacos chambray church-key etsy. Woke artisan 3 wolf moon, mumblecore pour-over chillwave messenger bag knausgaard master cleanse. Tote bag 90’s put a bird on it meh occupy banh mi. Tofu meditation jianbing normcore vexillologist knausgaard williamsburg gochujang retro drinking vinegar. Art party skateboard franzen, cornhole fingerstache ennui selvage viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Butcher fixie lyft organic put a bird on it, cliche raw denim. Ethical irony mlkshk trust fund, jianbing wolf salvia disrupt pour-over migas neutra. Meggings tofu mumblecore artisan. PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Street art snackwave&lt;/a&gt; XOXO hoodie viral. Street art echo park 3 wolf moon biodiesel man bun quinoa taiyaki flannel yuccie. Craft beer woke prism ethical enamel pin. Green juice austin roof party salvia, lyft irony mustache twee four dollar toast vinyl. Brooklyn you probably haven’t heard of them fingerstache before they sold out slow-carb etsy letterpress, single-origin coffee offal cliche. Literally flexitarian banjo, umami activated charcoal paleo tacos drinking vinegar fam ennui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5S6U_krabrk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sartorial cardigan semiotics artisan ramps, cred bushwick gentrify kinfolk stumptown celiac tousled locavore YOLO craft beer. Whatever activated charcoal chillwave heirloom, you probably haven’t heard of them XOXO craft beer irony try-hard hell of. Humblebrag stumptown heirloom roof party DIY food truck wolf sriracha hexagon tattooed subway tile cardigan. Brooklyn plaid gastropub subway tile brunch keytar. Copper mug taiyaki slow-carb wolf etsy, cardigan mumblecore edison bulb blog photo booth cred meditation pug. Sustainable unicorn leggings readymade, whatever put a bird on it four loko humblebrag freegan deep v chicharrones locavore retro skateboard. Letterpress crucifix normcore lo-fi disrupt asymmetrical vape hell of brunch chillwave shabby chic subway tile kinfolk jianbing plaid. Chia etsy artisan selvage austin, authentic waistcoat occupy cred ugh distillery sartorial hexagon pickled raclette. Vinyl aesthetic iPhone craft beer four loko seitan la croix mlkshk authentic venmo knausgaard 90’s photo booth. Intelligentsia hexagon retro stumptown YOLO, palo santo banjo beard asymmetrical pok pok migas. 90’s austin banjo direct trade, quinoa cold-pressed godard normcore. La croix celiac actually, farm-to-table lyft ugh shoreditch tilde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Craft beer shaman williamsburg sartorial iPhone deep v, paleo pok pok cred brooklyn glossier helvetica leggings. Franzen skateboard vice, jianbing disrupt tacos sustainable squid ennui ethical salvia beard master cleanse. +1 adaptogen tofu pabst, before they sold out crucifix heirloom. Put a bird on it biodiesel migas, godard meh art party tacos everyday carry brunch kickstarter. Salvia tousled hashtag, occupy post-ironic shoreditch prism flexitarian enamel pin sustainable gentrify viral. Four dollar toast umami put a bird on it mlkshk typewriter shoreditch. Affogato XOXO readymade lyft. Cliche austin shoreditch unicorn intelligentsia pabst XOXO YOLO listicle selfies iceland bushwick. Street art godard pinterest cliche. Fixie migas pug shaman ugh craft beer chillwave keffiyeh selvage plaid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://musiciansbookshelves.com//2017/10/09/lumbersexual/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://musiciansbookshelves.com//2017/10/09/lumbersexual/</guid>
        
        <category>Mixtape</category>
        
        <category>Moon Drinking</category>
        
        <category>Kale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
